Guide to the Yale Summer and Special Programs Records Concerning Faculty
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Yale Summer and Special Programs records concerning faculty
1985-1998
RU 1017
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
2.25
(3 boxes)
The records consist of personnel profiles, listings of courses, schedules, and correspondence documenting faculty in the Yale Summer and Special Programs.
Yale Summer and Special Programs
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 15-A (YRG 15-A), Central policy and administrative records of Yale summer and special programs.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The records were transferred from the office of Yale Summer and Special Programs, 2006.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the materials is restricted. See Collection Contents for details.
Arrangement
The records are arranged chronologically.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of personnel profiles, listings of courses, schedules, and correspondence documenting faculty in the Yale Summer and Special Programs.
Universities and colleges -- Faculty; Yale Summer and Special Programs; Yale University -- Faculty
- Records of the Yale Summer and Special Programs concerning faculty, 1985-1998; Accession 2007-A-055
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2074
  - Profile Forms, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Faculty Information, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Profile Forms, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Faculty Information, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Profile Forms, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Faculty Information, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Profile Forms, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Faculty Information, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Profile Forms, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Faculty Information, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Profile Forms, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Faculty Information, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Scholarships, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Profile Forms, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Faculty Information, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Profile Forms, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Faculty Information, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Profile Forms, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Faculty Information, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Profile Forms, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Faculty Information, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Profile Forms, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Faculty Information, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Profile Forms, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Faculty Information, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Faculty Information, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Personnel Profile Forms, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Personnel Profile Forms, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 28)